[Shaiapouf] Damn it. Almost.
[laughs]
It didn't take long
for the poison to kick in.
[Killua] What's going on?
He wasn't aiming for me,
which has to mean
he was aiming for the woman.
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[dramatic music playing]
[Knuckle] He's back.
Hey, uh, aren't we all too close?
Should I remove A.P.R. from Pouf
and then turn around
and go after the King?
Hurry. Hurry!
-[segment] Hurry.
-Hurry.
-Hurry. Hurry.
-Faster.
-Faster. Faster. Faster.
[Shaiapouf] There it is.
Come on. Hide it fast!
-[segment] Hurry.
-Hurry.
Faster.
-Faster.
-Faster!
-Faster. Faster.
-Faster.
-Hurry. Hurry.
-Hurry.
-Faster. Faster.
[Ikalgo] Hmm.
These two won't work.
They're way too mangled.
They'd make absolutely
terrible living dead dolls.
The King is at the palace's entrance.
-Yeah.
-We should go and circle around the wall
and hide ourselves among the crowd.
[Killua] Okay.
How 'bout Gon and Pitou?
Hold on.
So I'm curious.
How does that crystal work?
Do you see Pouf and me in it, too?
Yes. I have a bird's-eye view of you.
When I look at someone
with just my right eye,
my Wink Blue registers them
on the crystal.
After that, I can monitor them
anytime I like
by looking with just my left.
And I can only use my power
to watch three people at one time.
If I see someone else
with only my right eye,
I won't be able to see
the oldest of the three targets,
which, in this case, is Pouf.
and if you can only see his main body,
well, it's probably more
of a hindrance than a help.
And if his main body
is only the size of a fly,
Our only chance to defeat Pouf
is while he's divided.
Doesn't sound like
a disadvantage to me.
[wind blowing]
Now walk forward.
[cell phone buzzing]
[beeps]
[narrator] Noises echoed
throughout the old castle,
on the cell phone hidden in a pocket.
[Welfin] Sir Pitou, this is Welfin.
I'll try to keep this as brief as I can.
[Welfin] There are still intruders
all over the place,
so we're taking refuge
underneath the palace.
I'll let you hear her voice.
[latch clanks]
[groans]
[Shaiapouf] Since I can split myself
at the cellular level,
it's also possible for me
to become different people.
I can replicate faces,
bodies, even voices.
that will release him
from the curse of that girl.
So you should just keep watching
Gon and Pitou.
[latch clanks]
[tense music playing]
[wind blowing]
Now I want you to heal Kite
like you said you would.
[Neferpitou] Your name.
What did you say your name was?
Gon. It's Gon Freecss.
I owe you that.
This man…
[thud echoing]
[Neferpitou] Gon, the truth is
he died during our fight.
[shuddering]
I can't bring back the dead,
no matter what.
My ability has limits.
It can only prevent the body
from decomposing
and control its movements.
[sobbing]
[Neferpitou] His soul isn't here,
not anymore,
and I can't bring him back.
Your friend is gone.
I'm sorry.
Thanks a lot.
[gasps]
[sighs]
What is this?
Where did that come from?
Why are you thanking me?
Oh, drop it, already.
Stuff just means stuff, okay?
What was that all about?
Making me angry is an interesting way
of showing me your gratitude.
Don't worry about it.
That was the last time.
[groans]
Because we're friends.
[gasps]
I don't say thanks,
not to my friends.
I nearly forgot.
[gasps]
What is going on here?
Oh, Kite.
And now I've got this
pointless kill to my credit.
You sure have grown up, Gon.
[dramatic music playing]
It's me.
I did this.
From here on out,
in victory or defeat, it'll be hell.
[Gon] If I just hadn't gone with him…
Kite would still be alive.
[dramatic music playing]
[imperceptible]
It was…
it was all my fault.
[dramatic music playing]
[imperceptible]
If I hadn't followed him,
none of this would have happened.
It really was all my fault.
So it's all my fault that now Kite is…
But it was me.
It was… It was all me.
I killed Kite. It was all my fault.
All of this is my fault.
No! It's Pitou's fault!
He would never be beaten,
not by something like that.
Kite is dead now.
Kite is dead now!
Somebody help me.
Please, anybody, help me,
because Kite is… Because he is…
I'll fix you. I promise.
[shuddering]
[Neferpitou] Dr. Blythe.
[sighs]
Huh?
What's going on?
Is Pitou going to help Kite?
Of course. Kite was never dead.
Please, you can do that
after you finish healing Kite.
but something is wrong with Gon.
[Killua] What is it? What's wrong?
Kite is not being healed,
but it appears that Pitou is instead.
[gasps]
Gon is slumped over
on the floor next to Pitou.
[laughing]
[Gon] Please…
help Kite.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Anger and Light."
[Killua] Hold on until I get there.
[Gon] I don't care if this is the end.
I'm gonna kill you, Pitou!
[Killua] Gon! No!